http://www.midflorida.com/privacy-notice/

Skip to Content
What does MIDFLORIDA Credit Union do with your personal information?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security Number
Account Balances
Payment History
Transaction History
Overdraft History
Account Transaction
When you are no longer a member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information; the reasons MIDFLORIDA Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does MIDFLORIDA Credit Union share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes -
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes -
to offer our products and services to you.
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -
information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
We don't share
Questions?
Call toll free (866) 913-3733
What We Do
How does MIDFLORIDA Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
We also maintain other physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect this information and we limit access to information to those employees for whom access is appropriate.
How does MIDFLORIDA Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Our affiliates include:
Financial companies such as: MIDFLORIDA Insurance Services, LLC.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
MIDFLORIDA Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include securities broker dealers and insurance companies.
Questions?
Call toll free (866) 913-3733
Revised 02/2014
